okay now we're ready to mend it okay
ready here we go number 18 maybe you
want to do this one everyday one time
you
so relax your forehead put a little
smile on your face hold in your stomach
just a little bit tight relax your
fingers relax your eyelids check your
shoulders for a bit relax and then let's
come to our breath
long exhales let's not count to being
let's just watch the exhales long
exhales and bring the mind to the center
with the breath
then we'll start a meditation please
look into your heart and connect with
your heart teacher gears you know like
kind of sneak into the grain of sugar
and submit bills
and to be with them no special plan or
agenda just be quiet with them enjoy
being with you heart teacher
then during that three-day retreat we
won't use our cell phone and then when
we come out of retreat
I think it's Thursday or Friday we will
most of us will grab our cell phone and
text somebody WeChat somebody I'd like
you to think of two or three people that
you will probably contact with your cell
phone or your laptop after you get out
of the three-day retreat all of us have
some busy things we have to do we have
plans after this program but also after
the three days means we feel that we
will need to write someone text someone
WeChat so try to think of two or three
people that you might be sending us
reach out to as soon as you take down
your boundary markers or as soon as you
reach the temple okay here we go
and
in China each other imagine that someone
comes up to you and says oh that's a
nice cellphone and I heard about Huawei
cellphones and how does it work and then
you know we're not scientists and we
have a picture in our mind that we talk
into the phone we push a button and then
their circuit closes and electricity
goes across some wires and some of us
remember from 7th grade science class
electrons are moving to a pipe or
something and then somehow it comes out
of the phone as a signal and it goes and
touches tower cell phone tower then
there's more electrons moving in the
cell phone tower alone
copper wires and then another signal
goes out and goes to a satellite and
there's more wires in the Starliner more
electrons move and then signals come
from the satellite to my friend in
Singapore to my husband or my children
and that's how we explain a cellphone if
you and me had to make a cell phone it
would take a thousand years I think but
we have a rough idea how it works so get
in touch with that rough picture in your
mind mostly from seventh grade science
class about how the cell phone is
working because somebody asked your
question about it after you finished
your three-day retreat
how does a cell phone work
[Music]
and then try to take refuge which means
which always means look at the deeper
causes what makes the copper carry
electrons who made satellites go up into
space who built that cell phone tower
why am i able to communicate with people
I love and do things I think are
important with this cell phone and then
try to think about the real causes then
I don't know that clearly all the causes
but I I believe it must have to do with
helping other people to communicate now
maybe a husband and wife that you know
they have trouble communicating with
each other maybe you help them or maybe
you taught a child to read or you
explained your understanding of diamond
to other people you shared so try to
figure out yourself what has caused the
cellphone what keeps it working
now if you weren't meditating I would
ask you if you want to go deeper but
since you can't talk I I believe you
want to go deeper so you can take this
meditation to a deeper level and think
about messages you're getting nowadays
who's been writing you who's been
posting things that you mean what family
members of friends are using reach out
to contact you and think about some of
the messages you've gotten I try not to
read them before I go to bed because
some of them disturb my mind good ones
and bad ones mm you think about messages
you get on your cell phone and try to
understand that they are also coming
from you good ones that you're getting
nowadays bad ones what you see on the
internet this week news entertainment
all the content of your cell phone not
just a cell phone it's also coming from
you and from your scenes
and all this kind of thinking all this
kind of meditation is taking refuge
because it will protect you you can keep
yourself on working if you help others
to communicate and you can only get
beautiful messages and see inspiring
uplifting things on the internet if you
speak that way to other than you
communicate that way to others and
that's taking refuge
thank your mama in your heart that's
probably one of the main jobs that
enormous to keep you thinking like this
and then come back to your breath three
long exhale
and then study up in your high take a